嘿 货来晚了
Yo, the shit is late.
是啊 还在灌瓶呢
They're still vialing up.
通常卸来的货都是成品 不过这次得装瓶子
Usually come off the train street-ready, but this time they gotta vial.
伙计有样品吗?
Y'all got any testers, man?
- 有 等会儿 - 等会?
- Yeah, later. - Later?
有货吗 伙计
Got any testers, man?
哥们 现在连9点都没到 你就饥渴成这样
Nigger, it ain't even 9:00, and you fiending on it.
它妈的滚一边去
Get the fuck out of here, man.
该死的
Damn.
嘿 你干嘛这么对他?
Why you act like that?
你说那些狗娘养的吸毒佬啊?
What, for these junkie motherfuckers?
你整天榨取他钱 却当他是条狗?
So you just gonna take his money all day and treat him like a dog?
- 那我该怎么招呼他? - 我不知道
- How I'm supposed to treat him? - I don't know.
但是你不该那样凶他
But you ain't got to punk him like that.
他自作自受 他是个该死的瘾君子
He punked himself. He's a goddamn drug addict.
而你是个该死的毒贩子
And you a goddamn drug dealer.
那又怎样?
So?
那又怎样了?!
So what?
什么 "顾客永远是对的"?
What, the customer's always right?
我们在公房区 顾客各个无药可救
We're in the projects. The customer be fucked up.
你不该在乎这些黑佬 伙计
You can't give these niggers shit, man.
为什么不 为什么不行?
Why not? Why can't you?
操 其他行当做买卖就不会占人便宜
Shit, everything else in the world get sold without people taking advantage.
搞什么诈骗 扯谎 黑吃黑
Scamming, lying, doing each other dirty.
为什么这里就要这样?
Why has it got to be that way with this?
因为他们是吸毒的
'Cause they dope fiends.
没错 但是游戏不该那么玩
Yeah, but the game ain't gotta be played like that.
别跟我说不这样就做不成买卖了 非得互相掐架
You can't tell me this shit can't get done without people beating on each other...
互相动刀子 互相鄙视
Killing each other, doing each other like dogs.
不搞出那些名堂 这里就不用五分钟拉一次警报了
Without all that you ain't got 5-0 here on our backs every five minutes...
被条子追着不放
Throwing us around and shit.
操
Shit, man.
你以为条子在乎谁嗑高了?
You think 5-0 would care about niggers getting high?
在公房里?
In the projects?
哥们 条子来这是因为有尸体
Man, 5-0 be down here about the bodies.
那才是他们来这儿的目的 尸体
That's what they be down here about, the bodies.
哥们 公子哥们
Squires, young squires.
你想要什么 伙计
What you want, nigger?
一小袋子的时髦东西 伙计 一些给你们的时髦东西
A little bag of styles, man, a little bag of styles for you.
来看看 看看
Check it out.
只要5美元
Only $5
只要5美元 怎么样?
Only $5, what's up with that?
只要5美元 就能立马让你帅得冒泡
$5 make you a gallant motherfucker, right there, boy.
我们认识他
Him, we know.
火线重案组 第一季 第三集 交易
The Wire S01E03 The Buys
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
*Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
"王者为尊"  ---D'Angelo
这次闹事有什么后遗症?
What are we facing from the riot?
三个目击者的口供
Three witnesses' statements...
都称警员对年轻人攻击之前并未受到挑衅
All of them saying the officer's assault... on the youth was unprovoked.
你知道是怎么回事 长官
You know how that goes, Commissioner.
每次我们赢了战斗 大家总会联想到警察滥用暴力
People's idea of police brutality is whenever we win a fight.
检察官是怎么说的
What does the state's attorney say?
他说要交给大陪审团
He says it goes to a grand jury.
本丢·彼拉多：听命于教廷 审判耶稣的罗马行政官
他是现代版的本丢·彼拉多
That's him doing Pontius Pilate.
只要大陪审团不起诉 他就可以推得一干二净
The grand jury doesn't indict, he looks clean for passing the buck.
如果他们起诉了呢?
And if they do indict?
他们不会的
They won't.
三位目击者的犯罪记录
Criminal histories on our three witnesses...
一个比一个长
One longer than the next.
毒品 枪械 人身攻击...更多的毒品
Drugs, weapons, assault... more drugs.
混蛋们往好警察头上撒粪
Shitbirds throwing dirt at good police.
同样地 中尉长
Just the same, Lieutenant...
我希望你能反省一下 是出于什么策略
I want you to rethink whatever tactic led you
让你派了三名便衣刑警在临晨两点
To send three plainclothes officers to do field interviews
去高层居民区做实地调查
At the high-rises at 2:00 in the morning.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我想你们找了工会律师?
I take it your people have union counsel?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
长官 我请求...
Sir, I would request...
在大陪审团审查期间
That pending the grand jury review...
将Pryzbylewski警员安排放行政假(相当于停职)
Officer Pryzbylewski be placed on administrative leave.
我可以让他留在办公室
I can use him in-office,
但是在大陪审团有结果前 我们不应该再派他出警
But we shouldn't have him on the street until the grand jury signs off.
那脸真是丢大了
That's putting our tail between our legs.
我觉得我们正式的态度应该是...
I think our official stance has to be...
他在那里根本没有不当行为
He did nothing wrong out there.
一个14岁的孩子瞎了一只眼睛
A 14-year-old is half-blind.
我们也有两个人受伤了
And two of ours were injured as well.
说得没错 他们在那它妈的朝我们开枪
Goddamn right. They were fucking shooting at us out there.
Bobby 你觉得呢?
Bobby, what do you think?
让他别出外勤...
Keep him off the streets...
直到法院结案
Until it clears the courthouse.
好吧 那我们就等大陪审团的决议吧
Okay, then, we'll wait on the grand jury.
中尉 请留步
Lieutenant. A moment, please.
那里究竟发生了什么事?
What happened out there?
你知道他们在没有支援的情况下 去了高层公寓吗?
Did you know they were in the high-rises without backup?
如果我回答是的...我就失职了
If I tell you yes... I screwed up.
如果我回答不是...
If I tell you no...
就是把自己的手下陷于不利
I'm putting my men in the jackpot.
你还要我作答吗?
Do you still want me to answer?
我搞砸了 长官
I screwed up, sir.
好同志 愿意为大局挺身而出
Good man, willing to take one for the company.
去它妈的大局
To hell with the company.
我在这儿是为我的人辩护 如此而已
I'm defending my own people here, that's all.
Valchek警长的意思是 他感激你...
What Major Valchek means to say is that he's grateful that you...
能为Pryzbylewski警员着想 伸出援手
Extended your support on behalf of Officer Pryzbylewski.
- 他是个麻烦鬼 - 他不该出外勤
- Fuck-up that he is. - He should be off the street.
我能说什么? 这孩子需要...
What can I say? The kid needs...
一点指导 一点监督
A little guidance, a little supervision.
Stan觉得如果能让一个年轻警员重回街头...
Stan here thought that if he got a young officer back on the street...
也许能重头来过...
Where he might start over--
一个新的小队 新的队长
A new unit, a new lieutenant.
你瞧 也许能让他重新找到感觉
You know, that it might bring him around.
我明白他这次是搞砸了
I understand he messed up here.
我明白
I understand that.
所以我要对你说...
Which is why I'm saying to you...
我欠你一个人情...
I owe you...
如果他这次能过了大陪审团这一关
For walking him through this grand jury thing.
作为补偿 东南片会给你们送来
And to compensate, Southeastern is sending you
两辆全新的便衣警车 和一辆监视车
Two new unmarked units, and a surveillance van.
另外 你需要警力的话...
Plus, you need manpower...
在他们接受内部调查的这段时间里
While these guys are busy with this IID thing...
尽管开口
All you do is ask.
中尉
Lieutenant.
那么我们之间算是有交情了 Valchek?
So I've got suction with you, Valchek?
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm saying.
副局 随时乐意效劳
Deputy, always a pleasure.
塞翁失马 焉知非福
A necessary evil.
- 什么? - Valchek
- What? - Valchek.
如果我反问你 算不算犯上?
Is it insubordinate if I ask what's so necessary?
谢谢你没有踢走Pryzbylewski
Thanks for not cutting Pryzbylewski loose.
否则 部里就要被夹在Valchek和市政厅之间了
If you had, the department would be caught between Valchek and city hall.
我欠你一次
I owe you for that.
这个Barksdale...
This Barksdale...
他藏得很深
He's dug in.
也许光诱捕还不行
It may take more than buy-bust.
既然证人的事已经被媒体知道了...
And since it's been in the press about the witness--
这不算什么问题
It's not an issue.
坚持小范围调查
Keep it a tight little circle.
给我看看三周街头工作的成果 你会发现事情就过去了
Give me three weeks of good street work and you'll see this through.
几张重罪逮捕令 一些毒品做物证
A couple of felony warrants, a little dope on the table.
这些就足够了
That's all we need here.
没有任何证据明确表明
Under no circumstances is it accurate to suggest
此次谋杀事件
That this particular homicide
与被害人早先的出庭作证记录有关
Was the result of the victim having been a witness in an earlier case.
而提出相反论调的报道 也没有事实依据
Reports to the contrary are without factual merit.
你是说你能肯定这个男人的被害
Are you saying that you know definitely that this man was not killed...
- 不是由于他出庭作证? - 我们认为...
- because he testified? - We think that...
我是说 那个...
I mean, that is...
我们正在尝试以街头争斗的角度
We're looking into the possibility that Mr. Gant
调查Grant先生遇害案
Was involved in a street dispute.
所以自然此案绝对
Which, of course, would have nothing to do...
与他为数月前为已经结案的案子
With his being a witness...
出庭作证一事无关
In an unrelated case that concluded weeks ago.
但是目前你们还没有发现任何嫌疑犯?
But you haven't developed a suspect at this time?
不 我们还没有
No, we haven't.
Bunk 为你害臊 伙计
Bunk, shame on you, lad.
那你指望他怎么办?
What did you expect him to do?
我不知道 抢过麦克风 把Rawls推倒在地
I don't know, grab the mike shove Rawls to the ground,
大声宣告整个Baltimore应该一起来抗议
Declare that all of Baltimore should rise as one
因为他们在冷血地谋杀证人
Because they're murdering witnesses in cold blood.
听上去更像是你的作为
That sounds more like one of your moves.
查了他两个星期 我们连张照片都没有
Been working on him two weeks, we don't even have a photo.
它妈的太丢脸了
It's fucking embarrassing.
嘿 Pat
Hey, Pat.
有个活儿让你们去查查
We got a job for you guys to try to run down.
是什么?
What is it?
我们需要这个家伙的一张照片 Barksdale
We need a photo of this guy, Barksdale.
我们需要知道他长什么样
We need to know what he looks like.
那就去查查犯罪记录库
So go down to the B of l.
你们瞧 这是问题所在 伙计们
You see, that's the problem, guys.
Barksdale从没在成年后被逮捕过
Barksdale's never been arrested as an adult...
所以我们没有什么犯罪记录照片
So we don't really have a B of I photo.
他的未成年犯罪记录也被撤销了 所以也没有照片
He had his juvenile record expunged, so there's no photo there either.
那你玩完了
Then you're fucked.
是的 没错
Yeah, we are.
不过看在我们都来上班的份上
But seeing as we all came into work today,
我想管它呢 我们来试点别的 所以...
I thought, let's try something different. So...
我们知道他母亲的社区服务记录
We know from his mother's social service record...
Barksdale是在Franklin Terrace长大的 对吧
That Barksdale grew up in Franklin Terrace, right?
嗯 这让我想到...
It occurred to me...
出于对西Baltimore高层居民区的一知半解
Being vaguely familiar with the high-rises of West Baltimore...
公房项目出于安全考虑
That the housing project began to take photos...
开始对每位登记入住的居民拍照留底
Of every registered resident as a security measure.
我说得对吗 Greggs探员?
Am I correct, Detective Greggs?
是的
Yeah.
所以你想让我们去房管局 把他的照片调出来
So you want us to go down to the housing department and pull his photo.
一点没错
Excellent.
你瞧 我跟你 真是想到一块儿去了
You know, you and l, we think as one.
真像两匹并驾齐驱的骏马
We're like two horses together in a harness.
那你干嘛不自己去查?
Why don't you fucking do it yourself?
当然可以 只要你不介意坐在我的位置上 翻阅那些谋杀案的卷宗
Sure, if you don't mind sitting in my desk, reviewing homicide folders...
详细地做好笔记 努力找到一丝新的线索
Taking meticulous notes, trying to run down a few new leads.
这工作单调又繁重
It's boring, painstaking work,
但如果你不想跑去房管局
But if you don't want to travel to the housing department,
我愿意和你交换
I'll switch with you.
算了 Patrick 我们就走一程吧
Fuck it, Patrick. Let's take a ride.
真会给人打气
That was inspiring.
我可是个将才
I'm a leader of men.
嘿 生意怎么样?
Yo, What's up with shop?
补给没来
No re-up.
为什么?
Why not?
因为红帽卖玩了(装毒品的针剂瓶有个红色瓶盖)
'Cause we out of red caps.
Stink说明天我们会有新货
Stink say we gonna have a new package tomorrow.
- 新货? - 是的
- New package? - yeah.
是的 哥们 我们手上的玩意儿太次
Yeah, man, this weak-ass stepped-on shit
让那些瘾君子怨声载道
We got out here get these fiends agitated.
可瞧瞧他们 还在买呢
Look at them, they still buying it, though.
是啊 他们买了两倍的量 却只有原来一半的爽
Yes, they're buying twice as much and only getting half as high.
那是什么?
What was that?
车不能那么走
Castle can't move like that.
车只能上下或者左右
Castle move up and down or sideways like.
不 我们没玩那个
No, we ain't playing that.
看看棋盘 我们是在玩跳棋
Look at the board, we're playing checkers.
- 跳棋? - 是的 跳棋
- Checkers? - Yeah, checkers.
干嘛要在象棋的棋盘上玩跳棋?
Why're y'all playing checkers on a chess set?
你管得着吗 我们没有跳棋啊
Why do you give a shit? Man, we ain't got no checkers.
是啊 但是象棋更好玩
Yeah, but chess is a better game.
那又如何?
So?
不 等等 等等
No, hold up.
你们不会玩象棋 是吧?
Y'all don't know how to play chess, do you?
那又怎么样?
So?
怎样? 不怎么样 伙计
So? So, nothing, man.
如果你们想学 我愿意教你们
I'll teach y'all if you want to learn.
拜托 哥们 不要 我们正玩到一半
Come on, man. No, come on. We're right in the middle of a game.
别吵 我想看看
Chill out, I want to see this.
没有跳棋的棋盘 怎么玩跳棋呢
Y'all can't be playing no checkers on no chessboard.
好吧 好吧...伙计
All right..., man.
瞧 你看啊 很简单
Look, check it, it's simple.
看到这个了吗?
See this?
这个是核心
This is the kingpin. eh?
他就是王
And he the man.
你将了对方的军 你就赢了
You get the other dude's king, you got the game.
不过他也会想法子将你的军 所以你得保护它
But he's trying to get your king, too, so you gotta protect it.
这个王 他每次能走一步
Now the king, he moves one space...
随便朝哪儿 因为他是王
Any direction he damn choose,'cause he's the king.
像这样 这样 这样 好吧
Like this, this, this, all right?
但是不能越子
But he ain't got no hustle...
而剩下的他妈的同色棋子们
But the rest of these motherfuckers on the team...
会罩着他
They got his back.
由他们深入敌营 他就不用亲自上阵
And they run so deep, he really ain't gotta do shit.
就像你舅舅
Like your uncle.
是的 像我的舅舅
Yeah, like my uncle.
看到这个了吗? 这个是皇后
You see this? This is the queen.
她聪明 她好斗
She's smart and she's fierce.
想去哪儿就去哪儿  想走多远就走多远
She moves any way she wants, as far as she wants.
她办事雷厉风行
And she is the go-get-shit-done piece.
让我想到了Stringer
Remind me of Stringer.
手里的这个就是车
And this, over here, is the castle.
就像货仓
It's like the stash.
能这样走
It moves like this.
这样移动
And like this.
哥们 货仓不会动 伙计
Dog, stash don't move, man.
得了 想一想 这个星期 我们把货仓搬了几次?
Come on, think. How many times we move the stash house this week?
对吧? 每次我们换地方...
Right? And every time we move the stash...
我们都得动用点人手 保护它
We got to move a little muscle with it to protect it.
对 对 你说得没错
True, true. you're right.
好吧 那这些光头的小子是啥玩意儿
All right. What about them little bald-headed bitches right there?
这里的这些
These right here.
他们是小卒 就像是士兵
These are the pawns. They're like the soldiers.
他们这样走 每次只能走一格
They move like this, one space forward only...
除非交锋 那就会像这样...
Except when they fight. Then it's like...
或是这样
Or like this.
他们是打头阵的 会冲上战场
And they like the front lines. They be out in the field.
那你怎么才能当上王呢?
So how do you get to be the king?
不是那样的
It ain't like that.
瞧 王者为尊 明白吗
See, the king stays the king, all right?
大家各司其职 除了小卒
Everything stays who he is except for the pawns.
如果一个小卒...
Now if a pawn...
一路冲到了对方的底线
Makes it all the way down to the other dude's side...
他就能成为王后
He gets to be queen.
就像我说的 这个王后可不是省油的灯
And like I said, the queen ain't no bitch.
她哪里都能去
She got all the moves.
好吧 那么...
All right, so...
如果我让它到了底线 我就赢了?
If I make it to the other end, I win?
如果你看住了对方的王 将了他
If you catch the other dude's king and trap it,
那你就赢了
Then you win.
但是如果我让它冲到了底...
But if I make it to the end...
我就是最厉害的
I'm top dog.
不 不是那样的 瞧
No, it ain't like that, look.
小卒 伙计 在游戏里...
The pawns, man, in the game...
会很快被吃掉
They get capped quick.
它们会早早出局
They be out of the game early.
除非他们是些狡猾的小卒
Unless they're some smart-ass pawns.
Nagras：一个牌子 可携带式的小型盘式录音座
Nagras 你们它妈的能相信吗?
Nagras. Can you fucking believe this?
这玩意儿也太古董了吧
This shit is prehistoric.
物管科那还有什么玩意?
What else have they got down there in Property?
八轨迹磁带?Victrolas(牌子 留声机)? 这个部门它妈的就是个笑话
Eight-tracks? Victrolas? That fucking department's a joke.
我们得和联邦调查局联手
We got to get with the feds somehow.
他们有轻便的无线录音设备
They got light-weights, wireless micro-recorders.
是的 药管局有
Yeah, DEA got those.
如果哪天天热 我带着这个上 肯定会被他们看穿
If I wear this on a warm day, they're gonna know.
就算他们随便搜个身 我就曝光了
Even if they do a half-assed search, I'm done.
Nagras 老天爷
Nagras. Jesus.
你不能让他绑着这玩意儿去公房那卧底
You can't send his ass into the projects with this shit taped to him.
这完全行不通
That ain't gonna play.
我说...
I'm saying.
McNulty和这个姑娘...
McNulty and the girl...
缉毒科的那个拉子 他们主办这案子
The lezzer from narcotics, they've got the file.
- 你跟谁搭档? - McNulty
- Who are you partnered with? - McNulty.
但是他跟我没有往来 我也不想跟他有交集
But he don't have shit to do with me and I don't want nothing to do with him neither.
警长 我就是个车上的备用胎  还能跑到哪儿去
Major, I'm a fifth wheel on a car that's going nowhere.
调我回来吧
Bring me home.
快了
Soon enough.
瞧 你是我在这件案子里的眼线
Look, you're my eyes and ears in this mess, right?
我不想再要什么惊喜 像那篇新闻报道
And I don't want no more surprises, like that newspaper article.
如果McNulty还有其他那样的计划...
If McNulty's planning any more bullshit like that...
我得在事发之前告诉副局
I got to be able to tell the deputy before the shit flies.
然后你就能带着我欠你的情回来
Then you come home with a favor in your pocket.
会坏到哪儿去?
How bad is that?
中尉
Lieutenant.
明天Carver和Prez归队
You get Carver and Prez back tomorrow,
但是Prez会留在办公室里
But Prez is in-office.
解除武器 不出外勤 什么都没有
No police powers, no street work, nothing.
就算大楼着火 他也得呆在办公室里
If the building catches fire, he stays in the office.
那Herc呢?
What about Herc?
病假 起码得等到周一
Medical, until Monday at least.
我很好奇你要怎么摆平你的警力
I wonder what you gotta do to get thrown off this police force.
要是你不管好你自己 等着瞧吧
Keep on with some of your shit, you just might find out.
它妈的报备单在哪里?
Where are the fucking run sheets?
黑板后面
Behind the board.
你们又去喝了?
You all go for a taste?
我们去替你拿了照片 别瞎操心了 McNulty
We got your picture, don't you fucking worry, McNulty.
这是Barksdale?
This is Barksdale?
Avon Barksdale
Avon Barksdale.
我不这么觉得
I don't think so.
读我的嘴唇
Read my lips.
Avon它妈的Barksdale
Avon fucking Barksdale.
他的名字在文档里
His name's on the form in the file.
抱歉我要多问一句...
Excuse me for giving a shit...
但是我不得不注意到 这是一个中年白人男子
But I can't help but notice this is a middle-aged white man.
你想要别的 就给我另一个名字
You want something different, you give me another name.
那是唯一的Avon Barksdale
That's the only Avon Barksdale
在房管局的文件里
In the housing department files.
找到你的香烟了吗
You got your smokes?
它妈的祝你愉快
Have a nice fucking day.
也许他是白人
Maybe he's white.
不 我是说 真的 看看我们都知道了些什么
No, I mean, really. What do we really know?
"Avon Barksdale 31岁"
"Avon Barksdale.31 years of age.
"出生于西Baltimore Provident医院"
"Born Provident Hospital, West Baltimore...
"母亲Willette Jackson Barksdale"
"to Willette Jackson Barksdale...
"父亲不详"
"father unknown.
"在Baltimore市立学校上学"
"Educated Baltimore city schools."
住址就是他控制毒品交易的公房
Address is in the same public housing where he controls the drug trade.
没有照片 没有简介
No flash, no profile.
不知是从哪儿冒出来的
Pretty much comes up out of nowhere.
没有工作记录 没有我们能查的税收记录
No work history. No tax information we can look at.
名下没有车 没驾照
No cars in his name, no driver's license.
没孩子
No kids.
也没有前科
No priors either.
嗯 有条不确定的线人情报
Yeah, here's this vague CI information...
据称他住在郡郊区若干栋公寓里
That states he stays in various apartments out in the county.
当然 地址待定
Addresses undetermined, of course.
他住进不同的女朋友家里
He moves from girlfriend to girlfriend...
也许在纽约也有一个女朋友
Might have another girlfriend in New York.
他喜欢练身 年轻的时候曾在金手套俱乐部打拳击
He likes to work out and he used to box Golden Gloves when he was younger.
我在他身上查了两周 说句实话 我们一无所知
I've been working on him for two weeks and the truth is, we don't know shit.
金手套俱乐部?
Golden Gloves?
你怎么打听到的?
How did you hear that?
我不知道 我...
I don't know. i--
我想我是从药管局的档案里看到的
I think I got that from a DEA File.
或是从一个线人那
Or from a Cl...
声称那个时候认识他
Who claimed to know him way back when.
那你什么都记下了?
So you write everything down?
是的 每一件
Yeah, everything.
- 好东西 各位! - 蓝盖 蓝盖
- Goddamn bomb, y'all. - Blue-tops, blue-tops.
双短
Double shorts.
现货 伙计
In the hole, man.
有蓝盖 在找蓝盖吗?
Got blue-tops. Looking for blues?
现货 伙计
In the hole, y'all.
- 蓝盖 - 红盖
- Blue-tops. - Red-tops.
价廉物美
Got that chronic...
- 红盖 - 两支10元
- Red-tops. - Two for $10.
蓝盖 蓝盖
Blue-tops, blue-tops.
连续刺拳
Keep your jab moving.
右脚动起来 左右 左右
Move with your right. Left, right, left, right.
两击重拳
Two punches.
我有些问题要问你 Mack
I got a few questions I wanna ask you, Mack.
手别停 近身一点 伙计
Keep your hands moving, work to the body some.
你们的目标是谁?
So who's your target?
- Barksdale - 谁?
- Barksdale. - Who?
- Avon Barksdale - 从没听说过
Avon Barksdale. never heard of him.
问题就在这儿
That's the thing.
这个家伙控制了西边的公房区
This guy's got the Westside projects locked up.
他大概和12宗谋杀案有关 却完全不在警方视线内
He's tied to maybe a dozen murders, he's completely off the radar.
- Avon 什么来着? - Barksdale
- Avon, what was it? - Barksdale.
如果你这么说
If you say so.
药管局在NADDIS(毒品和危险麻醉药品信息库)里 有两三页关于他的信息
DEA has a couple of pages on him from NADDIS entries.
在NCIC(国家犯罪信息中心)里没有资料 没有成年后被捕记录
Nothing in NCIC, no adult arrests.
我从98年开始在联邦调查局查毒
I've been working drugs for the Bureau since '98.
我可以告诉你  我们这里也没有掌握他的资料
I can tell you, we got nothing on him that I know.
这小东西...
This little thing...
给你每周一笑
Is the smile of the week.
看这个
Watch this.
- 什么? - 那是什么?
- What? - What was that?
去门那边 去门那边
Get the door.
这可是建功立业的案子
It's a career case.
可惜这种时候不入老板们的法眼
Not that my bosses give a damn at this point.
为什么不?
Why not?
这些戴着手铐的家伙 没有一个是叫Osama的(本拉登)
All of them mopes in bracelets and not one of them named Osama.
我还是欠你个人情 你有什么要求?
I owe you, brother. What do you need?
几个轻便麦克风
A couple of lightweight body mikes.
无线 有远程录音功能
Wireless, remote taping capability.
- 就这些? - 是的
- That's all? - En.
我来的地方 能进入20世纪就很开心了
Where I come from, we're just happy to be in the 20th century.
谁在负责这案子 我可以去告诉我的队长
Who's running the case, so I can tell my squad supervisor?
Daniels 缉毒科的
Daniels, out of Narcotics.
好的 没问题
All right, no problem.
操! 该死的雨!
Shit! Fucking rain, man.
好了 好了 你们都知道怎么回事
All right, y'all know what the fuck this is.
- 全部靠墙排队 它妈的快点 - 快 走啊
- Up against the wall, hurry the fuck up. - Come on, let's go.
排到后面去 它妈的没时间浪费给你们
Go on to the back. Ain't got time for this shit.
有些红盖 一些样品 让他们去角落
Got some red-tops, some testers. Get them around the corner.
快点 带他们走 带他们走
Hurry up, take them around.
操 它妈的看我干嘛 都去角落那
What the fuck you looking at me for? Get your ass around the corner.
我要那个 那个好
I want that shit, that's good.
随便 拿了就走
Fuck and leave
跟上 跟上
Keep it moving.
伙计 看到了吗?
Man, you see that?
嗯
Yeah.
倒数第三间 那就是货仓
Third from the end. That's the stash.
真够简陋的 伙计
Some real raggedy-ass shit here, boy.
太松懈了
Very sloppy.
你孩子多大了?
How old are your kids?
Mike8岁 Sean10岁
Mike is 8, Sean's 10.
最难养的时候
That's the hard part.
是啊 最难养的时候 不过你瞧...
Yeah, that's the hard part, but you know....
你多久能见他们一次?
How often do you get to see them?
每隔一星期的周末
Every other weekend.
想争取更多 但是她一直反对
Trying to get more, but she's fighting me.
她干嘛在这事上反对?
Why would she fight you on that?
她是在报复
She's getting even.
报复?
Getting even?
你肯定在外面有花头
You must've been fucking around.
- 我只是说说 - 你说得没错
- I'm just saying. - You're right.
八九不离十
It's always the case.
如果一个女人想报复 外面肯定有猫腻
A woman wants to get even, there's something extra there.
嘿 Bubbs 既然你这么聪明 怎么还混得那么惨?
How come you got all this wisdom and your life's so fucking hard?
我自己也奇怪呢
I've been wondering on that myself.
那么你呢? 结过婚没?
How about you? You ever been married?
我说什么了
What'd I say?
如果你不想说 我可要说了
If you ain't gonna say anything, I am.
什么?
What?
如果你是条狗 那你发错情了
If you're a dog, you barking at the wrong pussy.
什么 我现在成狗了?
What, so I'm a dog now?
- 喵 - 嘿 Bubbles
- Meow. - Bubbles.
我和女人约会
I date women.
我们又有了个共同点 我也跟女人约会
We've got something else in common. I date women, too.
那么差不多刑侦科的人都发现了 除了我?
So pretty much everyone in CID has worked this out but me?
没什么好猜的 我告诉他们的
There wasn't nothing to figure out. I told them.
我猜我错过了新闻发布会
I guess I missed the press conference.
这总比让每个警察
It's better that than to have every police
每天轮番对你试探好
On three shifts hounding you every goddamned day.
- 警察就是狗 - 是的
- Cops are dogs. - Yeah.
不是说我在这里
It's not like I was walking around
挥着什么拉拉的大旗招摇过市
Waving some dyke flag in the air, or some shit.
我知道我看上去好像没定性
I know I look like I could go either way.
老天 是的 对 你是的
Lord, yes, you do. Yes, you do.
有些事得坦白了 才能过得了关
It was something I had to put out there to get through the day.
我早该知道
I should've known.
早该知道什么?
Should've known what?
我曾经和另一个女警共事过 唯一一个让我另眼相看的
I worked with one other female police officer who was worth a damn, only one.
- 是个拉拉 - 是的
- A lesbian. - Yeah.
一开始 你坐在你的巡逻车里
In the beginning, you're in your radio car,
一个人 执勤
Alone, working your post.
大多数女警都不会从车上下来
Most women aren't getting out of that car.
没错
Right.
除非身边的搭档出现
Not without side partners showing up.
她们感到恐惧 生理上的
They're intimidated, physically.
- 一定会的 - 你没有?
- They gotta be. - You weren't?
刚开始的时候会
Yeah, at first.
但我不是说那种初出茅庐的恐惧
But I'm talking about some old straight-out-of-the-academy-type scared...
你懂我说的吗? 我不打算一直恐惧下去
You know what I'm saying? I wasn't about to stay scared.
你瞧 当你受了一两次的打击之后
You know, you get your ass kicked once or twice
你开始明白这不算什么世界末日 对吧
You realize it's not the end of the world, right?
大多数女人 她们不想相信这点
Most of the women, they don't want to believe that.
一些男人也是 他们甚至不愿往那想
Some of the men, too. They don't even want to go there.
- 你觉得这是因为你是同性恋吗? - 我不知道
- You think 'cause you're gay? - I don't know.
但是当警察还有别的选吗?
But is there any other fucking way to police?
我只知道 我爱这份工作
All I know is I just love the job.
一共3块2
That'll be $3.20.
- 不用找了 - 谢谢 祝您过得愉快
- Keep the change. - Thanks, have a nice day.
嘿 Dee上来了
Yo, Dee coming up.
它们会去哪儿?
Where's it all go?
钱
The money.
所有的钱会去哪儿?
Where do all the money go?
两万二或者两万四 最多相差这点
$22,000 or $24,000, give or take.
从平房区收到的?
From the low-rises?
嘿 伙计 你肯定让你的手下忙个不停了
Damn, boy! You must have that crew humming.
我还不记得之前 有从大院里收到过那么多钱
I don't remember a day we ever got this much from the Courtyard.
今天甚至不是发薪日
It wasn't even check day.
你在那干得不错 Dee
You doing good out there, Dee.
如果能拿到新货 我们会做得更好
We'll be doing even better when we get that new package.
新货和老货都一样 伙计
New package, same as old, man.
- 说什么? - 没有什么新品
- Say what? - Ain't no new package.
只不过把原来的玩意儿 装进不同颜色的小瓶里
Just gonna put that same shit out in a different color gelcap is all.
也许再掺进点普鲁卡因(局部麻醉药)或者一些咖啡因
Might spike that shit with some procaine or some caffeine,
但其他部分都一样
But otherwise the same.
String 伙计
String, man,
大伙已经跑来跟我们说 那玩意儿一点都不给劲儿
People are already coming back on us telling us that shit is weak.
我知道 它是不给劲儿 但是哪个不是?
I know, the shit is weak. But shit is weak all over.
事实是 不管我们怎么称呼海洛因 最后都是卖
The thing is, no matter what we call heroin, it's gonna get sold.
东西纯 我们卖
The shit is strong, we're gonna sell it.
东西次 我们可以卖出双份的 你知道为什么吗?
The shit is weak, we're gonna sell twice as much. You know why?
因为吸毒的 不管怎么样都会下手
'Cause a fiend, he's gonna chase that shit no matter what.
没道理的 懂吗
It's crazy, you know?
我们越是差劲 钱挣得越多
We do worse, and we get paid more.
政府管得越严 照样天下太平
The government do better, and it don't mean no never mind.
这里的买卖 Dee
This shit right here, Dee,
永远都是这样
It's forever.
这是你的奖金
That's your bonus right there.
给自己买点平常不会买的
And you buy something that you wouldn't otherwise.
谢谢 伙计
Thanks, man.
好吧
All right.
你记得我吗
You remember me?
我记得你吗?
Do I remember you?
那天我在这里 你想我请你喝一杯
I was in here the other day, you wanted a drink.
我喝到了吗?
Did I get a drink?
恐怕没有
Afraid not.
那我为什么要记得你?
Then why would I remember you?
你想被记得 那当时就做得不对
You want to be remembered, you going about it the wrong way here.
好吧
All right.
Larry
老样子
The usual.
这是我舅舅的地盘
This here's my uncle's place.
你是Orlando的亲戚?
You kin to Orlando?
不是
No.
Orlando就像是前台 知道吧
Orlando's like the up-front man, you know?
我舅舅才是出资的人
My uncle's the money man.
你是哪里人?
Where you from?
本地人 Baltimore
Right here. Baltimore.
我知道Baltimore 但是具体哪里?
I know Baltimore, but, like, where?
你知道Turner Station吗?
You know Turner Station?
Dundalk边上 靠近Point
Down past Dundalk, near the Point.
原来是Point(Sparrows Point工业区)
The Point.
那 你是个乡村小妞
So, you're a country girl.
你是说郡吧
You mean county.
在我那儿 郡就是乡下
Where I'm from, the county is the country.
那是哪儿?
Where is that?
那么...
So...
你是给你舅舅干活咯?
Are you working with your uncle?
我是他的左膀右臂
I'm his right hand.
嗯 你是
Yes, you is.
你想和我们一起坐在监控车里吗?
You want to ride with us in the van?
不
No.
为什么不?
Why not?
你觉得是浪费时间?
You think it's a waste?
在毒品分销中最后加价倒卖的贩子
马仔和小孩 你只能看到这些
Touts and children, that's all you're gonna get.
Avon Barksdale对阵...
有了
Bingo.
你从哪儿搞来的?
Where did you get this?
来看看这身破烂
Now, look at this piece of shit.
我随时能上了 对吧?
I'm good to go, right?
过来 让我看看
Come here, let me see.
Sydnor探员的整套行头
Detective Sydnor's ensemble.
西面公房区最时髦的打扮
It's the latest in Westside Project wear.
你们有撕破过范思哲的棉纺裤吗
Have your torn cammies by Versace...
弄脏过拉尔夫劳伦(高级服装)的汗衫吗?
Stained sweatshirt by Ralph Lauren.
你的耳麦装哪儿了?
Where you miked?
在我裤裆里 哥们 我觉得他们不会摸到那里去 对吧
Down in my dick, man. I figure they ain't gonna go down there, right?
我不知道诶 Sydnor 你这么一转...
I don't know, Sydnor, the way you twirling around...
也许那是他们第一个会摸的地方(看你是不是真爷们)
Might be the first place they look.
操你妈
Fuck you.
我两天没洗澡 四天没刮胡子
I ain't showered in two days, I ain't shaved in four.
现在 我就是个不折不扣的脏混混
Right now, I am one ripe, nasty son of a bitch.
嘿 Bubbs
Bubbs.
你觉得呢?
What you think?
这是你的卧底?
This your man?
是的
Yeah.
在你眼里 他够衰了吗?
Is he low-bottom enough for you?
衣服够破了...
Clothes is tore down enough...
他可以搞得再脏点 邋遢点
But he could use a little bit more stains, more dirt.
这里呢 伙计?
What's this here, man?
这是我的婚戒
It's my wedding ring.
操 你娶的是针筒 小子
Shit, you married to the needle, boy.
如果真是瘾君子 那玩意儿早就被当了
That shit been pawned off, if you for real.
这可是彻底的暴露
It's a dead giveaway.
你可以再减个20磅
You could stand to lose about 20 pounds,
把牙齿弄黄点...
Some yellow in your teeth...
手上搞些新伤口
Fresh bleeds on your hands.
好吧 也许我该到外头去  吸个一两年毒 是吧?
Okay. So maybe I should go out and shoot up dope for a year or two, right?
到那时候带着那副鬼样子回来
Come back when I can carry the look off?
我只是说说 伙计
I'm just saying, man.
看起来越是邋遢 越是逼真
The more tore down you look, the better.
只要进入他们的地盘 他们什么都会查
You going down in them towers, they gonna check everything.
那鞋子呢?
How about the shoes?
我知道你肯定对它们没意见 看看它们有多破
I know you ain't got no problem with the shoes, fucked up as they are.
让我看看鞋子 伙计
Let me see the shoes, man.
瞧
See?
你走进公房区的巷子
You walking down them alleys of the projects
你会踩在"亡士"上
You stepping on the dead soldiers.
"亡士"?
Dead soldiers?
是的 空瓶子
Yeah, empty vials.
只要走在Baltimore的街上  那些东西就会轧你的鞋底
You can't walk down a Baltimore street without them cracking underneath your feet.
你想知道他是不是真的瘾君子...
You want to know if a fiend is for real...
看看他的鞋底
Check the bottom of his shoes.
好吧
Okay.
在我们出发之前 先让他去踩踩空瓶
Have him dance on some empties before we go out there.
否则全完蛋
Get us killed.
他让你难过了?
He hurt your feelings?
有点
A little bit.
操
Shit.
四次交货...
Four hand-to-hands...
我两次 Bubbs两次  距离不远 都记下了
Two to me, two to Bubbs, with me close enough to mark it.
从谁那儿?
From who?
大多数是小孩子 小混混
Kids, mostly. Young-ass hoppers.
是个开头
It's a start.
这里很严密 Kima
They're pretty tight out here, Kima.
如果你不能把钱给对人...
If you don't hand no money to nobody that matters...
也就不能从他们手里拿到货
You don't get no product from nobody that matters.
你想回去吗?
You want to go back in?
该死的 我们把这里的货买了个遍
Shit, we copped from every crew out here.
我们是不是该换个地方 消化了它们?
Ain't we supposed to go off somewhere and fire this shit up?
嗯 让我们先离开这儿吧
Yeah, let's get the fuck out of here.
好吧
Well, now.
在你把钱给出去之后 有看到钱到哪去了吗?
Did you get to see where the money went after you handed it off?
没有
No.
这里只有马仔和跑腿的
Nothing but touts and runners here.
不过又一次 你早说过了
But then again, you told us so.
我没有那么说
I didn't say that.
但实际上...
But as a matter of fact....
其他人都出去了?
Everyone else roll out?
我...
I--
你去了楼上 不在这里
You were upstairs and out of pocket,
所以我就放他们回去了
So I cut them loose.
没关系 明天我再告诉他们
Just as well. I'll give them the news tomorrow.
出什么事了?
What happened?
我告诉副局我们搞了几次钓鱼
I told the Deputy we had a few hand-to-hands.
针对那些马仔
Low-level people.
他要我们整理好资料开展抓捕
He wants us to put everything into search-and-seizures
周三下午对公房区展开行动
And hit the projects Wednesday afternoon.
- 中尉 - 我知道
- Lieutenant. - I know.
你觉得那会让我们抓住Avon Barksdale吗?
Does he think that's what gets us Avon Barksdale?
我们伪装的买家 现在连大院都没进呢
The buys we made, they don't even go past the courtyards.
把所有钓鱼行动的资料都梳理一遍
Scratch together everything we got from the hand-to-hands...
输进电脑 申请许可证
And shape it into PC for the warrants.
起码 要有几个地点
A few locations, at least.
但是我们连要撞哪扇门都不知道
But we don't even know what doors to hit.
我们只发现一些平房的公寓 也许被用来做了货仓
A few apartments in the low-rises that we've seen used for stash.
那就写那些
Then we write on those.
中尉 这些家伙每隔一天就会换货仓
Lieutenant, these guys change stash houses every other day.
瞧 上头想看一场"马戏"
Look, the man upstairs wants to see a circus.
从现在起的几天后 我得给他看"三环表演"
A couple of days from now, I got to show him three rings.
老天爷
Christ.
抱歉 我们得行动了
I'm sorry. We gotta jump.
搞什么 这个副局没脑子吗?
What, is the Deputy Ops stupid?
不是
No.
这真是蠢到家了
This shit is fucking stupid.
如果我们能抓到几个人 他把他们送到法官面前
Not if we bring in some arrests he takes them to the judge,
他觉得法官就会罢手
He figures the judge goes away.
然后这案子就葬送在他手里了
And then he buries the fucking case.
我们要怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
没什么能做的 除了快点想出起诉罪名
There's nothing you can do, except pound out some probable cause.
- 它妈的我们整晚都得耗在这里了 - 我不会
- We're gonna be here all fucking night. - I'm not.
- 你它妈的要去哪儿? - 不 我是说 我办不到
- Where the fuck you got to go? - No, I mean, I can't.
我不会帮他们就这么黄了这案子 抱歉
I'm not gonna help them gut the case. I'm sorry.
我知道他是你的队长 你得听他的
I know he's your lieutenant. You gotta do what you gotta do.
但是我咽不下这口气了
But I can't swallow this shit anymore.
你来这干嘛?
Why are you here?
我在想事情
I'm thinking about something.
我能进来吗?
Can I come in?
不行
No.
不行?
No?
怎么了 McNulty? 从来没人对你说"不"吗?
What's the matter, McNulty? No one ever tells you "no"?
抱歉 我该先来个电话
Sorry. I should've called.
要怎么才能克隆一个传呼机?
How do you clone a beeper?
- 什么? - 我是想知道这个
- What? - That's what I need to know.
你9点上门找我就是为了问这个?
You show up at my door at 9:00 to ask me that?
他们用传呼机 对吧
They're using pagers, right?
其他毒贩都用手机 而他们却用呼机
Every other drug dealer has a cell phone, and these guys are all on pagers.
你想干什么?
What do you want to do?
Bunk和我 在抓那个Barksdale的小子时
Bunk and me, when we jack up the Barksdale kid...
发现他有个摩托罗拉的呼机
He's got a Motorola pager.
我们还给了他 免得他起疑
We give it back, so as not to spook him.
你想要克隆它?
You want to clone it?
有没有办法既不给传呼台发传票  又能搞定?
Can we do that without a subpoena to the pager company?
看看吧
Read that.
- 是什么? - 一份立案宣誓书
- What is it? - Affidavit from a state police case.
如果法官签了这样的东西 你就能克隆一台呼机了
A judge signs something like that, you can clone a beeper.
神啊
Christ.
合理的理由 同时准备好没完没了的说明
Probable cause, coupled with an exhaustion argument.
你得给法官看 其他的调查方法都失败了
You've got to show the judge that other investigative methods have failed.
你还需要一个长官 同意你去克隆一个嫌犯呼机
You'll also need a supervisor who wants you to clone a suspect's pager...
知道也许下一步会是...
Knowing that it might lead to
谁知道还是什么 笔式记录器 窃听装置
Who knows what else pen registers, wiretaps.
Daniels会上钩的
Daniels will come around.
Daniels会爆了你菊花
Daniels will have your ass.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 就这样? - 什么?
- That's it? - What?
不
No.
让我搞明白
Let me understand.
你有老婆的时候  在Best Western(连锁旅馆)里约会
You're married, and a date's a room at the Best Western.
现在单身了 约会就是不请自来  声称要了解
Now you're single, and a date is you coming over unannounced
怎么能合法截取一台呼机的信息?
To learn the legal requisites for a pager intercept.
差不多
Pretty much.
不
No.
好吧 我听明白了
Okay, I hear you.
你?
You?
好像你在乎似的
As if you give a shit.
你是个混蛋 McNulty
You're an asshole, McNulty.
我它妈的干什么了?
What the fuck did I do?
那批货还剩多少?
How much more to that pack?
50...60瓶
50, 60.
补给来晚了
Re-up's late.
让Wallace再给Stinkum发个传呼
Have Wallace hit Stinkum on his pager again.
有什么想吃的外卖吗?
You want something from carry-out?
嗯 鳟鱼堡
Yeah, lake trout sub.
掏钱
Pay up.
该死的
Damn.
你问了 我以为你请客呢
You asked, I thought you was treating.
你想错了 我又不是开银行的
You thought wrong, I ain't no bank.
小气劲倒是一样
You stingy like one.
- 看好了 别少给 - 嗯
- Just make sure you give me enough. - yeah.
不要蛋黄酱 加辣 来点饮料
No mayo, extra hot, something to drink.
好的
All right.
- 他是去买吃的? - 没错
- He's going for food? - Yes.
为什么不叫我 我肚子饿的他妈的直叫唤
Why didn't you tell me? My stomach's growling like a motherfucker.
饿着吧 哥们
Starve, nigger.
操
Man, shit.
补给来了
Re-up's here.
Stink 你好吗
Stink, what up?
你好 伙计 10分钟
What's up, bro? 10 minutes.
- 10分钟? 好 - 嗯
- 10? All right. - Yeah.
谁在里面?
Who's there?
你们给我掩护 听见了吗?
Y'all got my back, you heard?
它妈的进去
Get the fuck in there.
它妈的蹲下
Get your ass down.
它妈的坐下 它妈的快坐下
Sit your stupid ass down. Get the fuck down.
操 呆在那儿别动 婊子
Shit, stay there, bitch.
趴下 它妈的趴下 混蛋
Get down, get the fuck down, motherfucker.
东西在哪儿?
Where it at?
这里什么都没有
Ain't nothing here.
它妈的把你的手拿开
Get your fucking hand off.
在哪儿 伙计?
Where it at, man?
操!
Shit!
操! 我的腿!
Fuck, my leg!
它在哪儿 矮冬瓜?
Where it at, shorty?
厨房 水池下面
Kitchen, under the sink.
过去拿过来
Go on and get that.
有两千 我们撤
Two G-packs. Let's roll.
只有两千?
Just two?
- Omar 走啦 - 搞什么...
- Come on. - What the--
蠢货
Stupid.
操!
Shit!
我们它妈的赶紧撤
Let's get the fuck out of here.
操!
Shit!
拜托 Poot
Come on, Poot.
操!
Fuck!
那么 你的人看到他们被打劫了?
So, your man saw them get jacked?
是的 部分过程
Yeah, part of it.
他记下了车牌?
And he gets the tag number?
Bubbles是好样的
Good man, that Bubbles.
听着
Listen up.
西区警队会在Mount Claire的 停车场跟我们碰头
Western uniforms will meet us in the Mount Claire parking lot.
我们从那儿出发 然后长驱直入
We start there, and we don't stop until we take the doors.
我希望那些望风的越来不及报警越好
I want their lookouts to have as little chance as possible.
你呢?
What's with you?
我办公室
My office.
- 我不会去 - 你敢抗命?
- I'm not going. - You're insubordinate?
我不会去干会葬送这案子的事
I'm not jumping out on something that will harm the case.
你要是想打我报告 你随意
You want to write me up on that, you can.
你以为我想吗?
You think I want this?
副局一直在这案子上压着我
I got the Deputy Ops on my ass for this shit.
现在你在整个专案组面前给我好看
Now you show me up in front of the whole detail.
我没想给谁脸色看
I don't mean to show anybody up.
- 穿上防弹衣 - 不
- Get your vest on. - No.
我还有案子要查
I got police work to do.
狗娘养的 你既然想这样 干嘛不请病假?
If you felt this way, why didn't you call in sick?
我没病
I'm not sick.
不 你病了
Yeah, you are.
给我个请假单 说明你为什么身体不舒服 以至于不能参加今天的行动
Give me a 95 on why you are physically unable to participate in today's action.
什么 要我说谎 好让你保住面子?
What, I'm gonna lie so you can save face?
快 写下来
Come on, write it up.
"我不能参与小组行动,因为我肚子疼"
"I can't jump out with my unit because my tummy hurts."
我不会帮你这么结掉案子
I'm not gonna help you gut this case.
如果你想假装还是个警察 那你自便吧
If you want to pretend to be police, you go ahead.
我们行动
Let's do it.
我来了
I'm up.
你还在病假中
You're on medical.
我能上 老板
I'm up, boss.
给他一件防弹衣
Give him a vest.
不 混蛋
No, motherfucker.
又不是只有Stinkum一个能当保镖
It ain't just up to Stinkum to be muscle.
整个Pit都是你的
You got the Pit.
你们的人应该准备好接货
Your people supposed to be ready for the re-up.
你本该为他震场子
You supposed to be steady for him.
但是你在哪儿?
But where you at?
你在该死的三明治店里
You in the goddamn sandwich shop.
你有2万的货 Dee 进了你的场子
You got $20,000, Dee, coming into your shop...
你它妈的连看都没看到一眼
And you ain't even around to see that shit right.
- 瞧 我以为补给... - 不 想想你没做到什么
- Look, I thought re-ups-- - No, thinking was what you wasn't doing,
让我们现在看上去像娘们  你懂我的意思吗?
And now we look like bitches. You feel me?
我们得报复他们
We got to come back on them.
你却连是谁都不知道
And you can't even tell me shit about who they was.
其中一个叫Omar
One of them was named Omar.
Omar?
Omar 我听到有人这么喊他
Omar, that's the name I heard.
他们有辆白色的面包车
And they had a white van.
是的 我看见那面包车了
Yeah, I saw the van--
什么样的?
What kind of van?
5-0(条子)
Five-0.
5-0
- 抄错门了 - 是吗?
- Wrong door. - Yeah?
是的 昨天我们换了
Yeah, switched it yesterday.
让我看到你们的手
Let's see your hands.
让开 让我看到你们的手
Get out of the way. Let's see your hands.
起来 混蛋 起来 转过去
Up, motherfucker, up. Turn around.
都跟上
All the way up.
警察
Police.
把手举起来 举起来!
Put your hands up. Put them up!
猴子屁股转过去 把你手放到后面
Turn your monkey ass around. Put your hands at your back.
你干嘛跟我们过不去 伙计
Why you fucking with us, man?
拜托 伙计 该死的 我什么多没做
Come on, man, damn, I wasn't even doing shit.
拜托 伙计
Come on, man.
拷了他 拷了他
Cuff that one, and that one.
狗娘养的 感觉如何
Motherfucker, how's that feel?
你它妈的死定了
You fucked up now.
你爽了吗?
You feel it, right?
喜欢被这么揍吗?
How that feel?
你怎么不扭了?
Why you ain't swinging?
狗娘养的
Motherfucker.
来啊 再逞能啊! 混蛋 来啊!
Go ahead, play that cowboy shit, motherfucker. go ahead.
按住他 抓住他的手
Hold him down. Hold his arms!
腿趴开了 别逼我也揍你一顿
Spread your legs. Don't make me kick your ass, too.
混蛋
Come on!
抓住他
Get him.
叫你打警察
You don't hit a cop.
你脑子进水了 小子? 叫你打警察
What's wrong with you, boy? You don't hit a cop.
如果你来得更早点 你就能看一场打戏了
If you'd been here earlier, you'd have seen a beating.
没东西 它妈的屁都没有
Clean. Not a fucking thing in there.
随便撞的这里的门 能有什么机会?
Pick any door in the low-rises. What are the chances?
2频道想知道她能不能拍摄一些我们搜捕的地方
Channel 2 wants to know if she can film some of the places we raided.
她说不论我们搜到了什么  都会放进片子里
She says whatever we got, she'll put on film.
我们有什么?
Whatever we got?
毒品 手枪
Drugs, weapons.
我们什么都没有
We ain't got shit.
我打赌你肯定没进过巡逻队
I can tell you were never in patrol.
没错
Right.
- 抱歉我迟到了 - 什么事?
- Sorry I'm late. - What's up?
我不想当着那姑娘的面跟你说
I didn't want to tell you in front of the girl,
毕竟她也是缉毒科出来的
Her being from Narcotics and all.
Daniels不干净
Daniels is dirty.
什么?
What?
办你案子的家伙 他自己不干净
The guy running your case, he's got dirt on him.
你知道?
You know this?
去年你们局子为了他来找过我们
Your own agency came to us with concerns about him last year.
廉政问题
Integrity questions.
他们不想搞成内部调查 因为...
They didn't want to go to lnternal Affairs.
那个部门的漏洞多个像筛子
That office leaks like a sieve.
何况要是案子跟他们性命攸关 他们才不会办
Plus they couldn't handle a case if their lives depended on it.
也是
That, too.
你们专门查了Daniels?
You looked at Daniels specifically?
我们搞了两个月的资产调查
We did a two-month assets investigation.
这家伙有几十万的流动资产
The man has a couple hundred thousand more in liquid assets...
不是一个中尉长能挣到的
Than any police lieutenant should ever have.
也许他去了大西洋城(赌城)
Maybe he goes to Atlantic City.
说真的 你查过他背景了?
Seriously. You look at his background?
也许他有别的收入来源
Maybe he's got other sources of income.
也许有 但是我们没有机会深入调查
Maybe ?. We never got the chance to go further.
为什么没有?
Why not?
我们找了你们的副局长  告诉了他我们掌握的情况
We went to your Deputy for Operations and told him what we had.
你告诉了Burrell?
You took it to Burrell?
他说"谢谢 接下来就交给我们吧"
He says, "We'll take it from here."
所以我们就回来等着看好戏
So, we backed away and waited for something to happen.
等到现在
And waited.
那是一年前的事?
That was a year ago?
也许更早之前
Maybe more.
那个混蛋仍旧负责缉毒科
And that fucker's still the Supervisor for Narcotics.
你给我说说 是怎么回事
So, you tell me what the hell's going on.
反正
Anyway,
既然他在负责你们的案子 我想你会想知道
If he's running your case, I just thought you'd want to know.
谢谢
Thanks.